

Husni Mubarak
Ailatat
Frontend Developer

How to reach me:

Cell:

082134510421

Email:

husniailatat@gmail.com

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/husni-mubarak-ailatat-7186a2114/

Address:

Bangunjiwo, Kasihan, Bantul, Yogyakarta

Personal Profile

I am a Frontend Developer with more than 4 years experience. Have the ability and experience in designing, developing, and testing websites and mobile apps with the latest technology. Have experience using the programming language Javascript, PHP, C#

Education

Universitas PGRI Yogyakarta

S1 Teknik Informatika

My Skills

- Javascript
- Typescript
- React / Next JS
- React Native
- Node JS / Express
- PHP
- Laravel
- Codeginiter
- · ASP.Net Core

Work Experience

Frontend Engineer

Gramedusa Maret 2022 to present

- Building and developing websites and mobile apps
- Optimizing performance apps
- Collaborate with UI/UX on feature design and implementation

Frontend Developer

PT Grahatour Maret 2020 to Februari 2022

- Building and developing websites and mobile apps
- Optimizing performance apps
- Collaborate with UI/UX on feature design and implementation

Frontend Developer

PT Ramcou Buana Informatika Juli 2018 to Desember 2019

- Modify an existing website and mobile to upgrade the interface tested and refined software prior to rollout
- Building and developing android apps
- Provide time estimates to the tech lead or project manager and help identify tasks for developing the project plan as needed